schoolcashonline.com 2017-06-06

# SchoolCashOnline.com: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Effective Date: 10/28/2016

**KEV Group  
School Cash Online Website Privacy Policy**

KEV Software Inc. and KEV Group Inc. (collectively, “KEV Group”) take privacy and data security seriously. We are committed to transparency in the collection and use of your personal information. The Privacy Policy below describes how we use personal information, and the circumstances under which we may share this information. This Privacy Policy applies to the privacy practices of KEV Group on its School Cash Online website, located at [http://www.schoolcashonline.com](http://www.schoolcashonline.com/).

_**Collection and Use of Personal Information**_

_Information You Provide to Us_

  * **Account Registration and Sign In:**

You do not have to register for an account to visit our School Cash Online website. You must register for an account to access some of the features offered through our website, such as making payments to your child’s school and approving school permission forms. When you register, we collect certain information from you, including personal information such as your full name, email address, physical address, and a username and password that you select. You may also choose to provide your phone number. Your email (or other username) and password are used to allow you to login to your account. We also collect your response to a specific security question (e.g., your maternal grandmother’s maiden name), which we may use as necessary to help verify your identity.

Your registration information is used to set up and otherwise administer your account. You can edit and update your personal information in your account settings.

  * **Adding a Student:**
  
Registered users may add a student to their account. If you add a student, we collect the student’s full name, date of birth, school board district, and school. Depending on the school board and school, you may also be asked to provide a student number, a PIN number associated with the student, or other information as determined by a student’s school or school board. We also collect the nature of your relationship with the student (i.e., parent, legal guardian). We use this information (i) to confirm that you have been identified by the school or school board as eligible to add a student to your account, and (ii) to add the student to your account on the website

  * **Fees and Payments:**
  
Within your account, we post the school fees and other information associated with the student(s) who are added to the account as described in Adding a Student above. These fees are determined and posted by relevant schools or school boards. In order to make a payment, we collect your full name, phone number, email, billing address, and any additional details relevant to the fee selected (e.g. field trip lunch option, type of milk selection).

When you make a payment, we also collect personal information based on the payment method you select, as identified below:

    * eCheck: account type, institution number, transit number, and account number.
    * Credit Card: credit card type (i.e. Visa, MasterCard, American Express), credit card number, expiry date, security code and the name on the card.
    * myWallet: you can select the myWallet feature to access funds that you have already deposited to your account to make a payment.

We use this information to process any payments made through the website and to provide you with a payment history and record of payments. Your personal information is also used to set up any scheduled or recurring payments you select. If your payment is a donation, we may use your information to generate a tax receipt.

Please note that if you use Interac Online or PayPal for fees and payments, including for myWallet payments as described below, you will be re-directed to third party websites to make a payment. These websites are not owned or controlled by us and therefore we have no control over and are not responsible for the manner in which these third parties process personal information. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies on these third party websites.

  * **Forms:**
  
To complete a permission or other type of form for a student on your account, we collect your name, relation to the student, other information as may be requested for the form submission, and consent for the activity in question if applicable. 

  * **Communications:**
  
When you register for an account, you may select if you wish to receive email marketing communications with updates, surveys, and other information regarding School Cash Online. We may also send you transactional communications such as information regarding your payments, account administration and customer service requests.

You can opt out of receiving marketing emails from us using the opt-out or “unsubscribe” instructions provided in the communication. Alternatively, you may contact our Privacy Officer at [privacyofficer@kevgroup.com](mailto:privacyofficer@kevgroup.com?Subject=Re:Unsubscribe). Please note that even if you opt out of receiving marketing emails from us, we may continue to send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about our ongoing business relationship with you.

  * **Surveys:**
  
From time to time, we may offer you the opportunity to participate in one of our surveys or other customer research. We use this information to help us enhance our service offerings.

If you submit a technical support request, we may use your email to send you a survey asking about the quality of support that you received. We use survey responses to monitor and improve our technical support offerings.

  * **Contests and Promotions:**
  
If you choose to enter a contest or participate in a promotion, we may collect your name, address, phone number, and any additional information or content required for the contest or promotion, or that you otherwise provide. We use this information to administer the contest or promotion. As part of a contest or promotion, we may also share or otherwise publish the content you submit. Please refer to the privacy notice and the terms and conditions relevant to each contest or promotion to learn more about how we may collect and use information you submit in conjunction with that contest or promotion.;

  * **Contact Us:**
  
When you contact us with a comment, question or complaint, we collect the information you provide such as your name, username, email address, school, school board, along with additional information regarding the issue that we may need to help us promptly answer your question or respond to your inquiry. We retain this information to assist you in the future and to improve our customer service and service offerings. We also use personal information to establish and manage our relationship with you and provide quality service.

_Information We Receive from Schools or Schools Boards_

KEV Group provides software as a service to schools and school boards to help them manage school fees. We receive personal information regarding students from schools and school boards in order to provide our services, including student name, date of birth, gender, address, phone number, school board district, school, grade level, homeroom number, course enrollment, student identification number, and parent/guardian information. 

We use this information in order to administer our service, including assigning school fees to the appropriate School Cash Online accounts, facilitating payment for such fees, and obtaining and administering permissions. 

_Information We Collect Automatically_

We and our third party service providers, including Google Analytics, collect, process, store and analyze information obtained from your browser, including IP address, device identifiers, browser characteristics, operating system details, language preferences, referring URLs, length of visits, and pages viewed. We also use “cookies” or other tools that track, measure and analyze the behaviors and usage patterns of visitors to the School Cash Online website. We use this information to help us understand how visitors engage with the School Cash Online website and to improve our visitors’ experience. We also collect and use IP addresses to help verify our users’ identities when submitting forms and permissions. 

A cookie is a tiny element of data that the School Cash Online website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer or mobile device so we can recognize you when you return. We use cookies for analytics purposes as well as for certain features of the School Cash Online website. If you have created an account on the School Cash Online website, cookies may let us know who you are, and provide us and our service providers with information that we will use to personalize your visit. You may set your web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to not accept certain cookies. However, if you decide not to accept cookies from the School Cash Online website, you may not be able to take advantage of all of the features of our website.

You can obtain additional information on Google Analytics’ [collection and processing of data](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) and [data privacy and security](https://support.google.com/analytics/topic/2919631?hl=en&&ref_topic=1008008), including how to [learn more about opting out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) of Google Analytics’ data collection. 

Your web browser may have settings that allow you to transmit a “Do Not Track” signal when you visit various websites or use online services. Like many websites, this website is not designed to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from browsers. You can learn more about “Do Not Track” signals [here](https://allaboutdnt.com/).

**_Sharing of Personal Information_**

We do not sell or share your personal information with third parties without your consent except as set forth in this Privacy Policy and as required or permitted by law.

_Schools and School Boards_

We share information regarding account holders and students such as fees paid, amount of payment, donations made and permissions granted with the student’s respective school and/or school board in order to provide our service. We may also share information with school boards as necessary to help verify an individual’s eligibility to add a student to their account.

We may also share information such as a name and email address regarding individuals who have purchased an item from a school or school board (e.g., tickets to a school fundraising concert open to the public) so the school or school board can administer the item (e.g., delivery of tickets). 

_Service Providers_

Your personal information may be transferred (or otherwise made available) to our affiliates and other third parties who provide services on our behalf. We use third parties to assist with payment processing, to provide technical support and solutions, and to host and manage our website. Our service providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and are not authorized to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes.

Your personal information may be maintained and processed by us, our affiliates and other third party service providers in the US or other jurisdictions. In the event that personal information is transferred to the US or other foreign jurisdiction, it will be subject to the laws of that jurisdiction and may be disclosed to or accessed by the courts, law enforcement and governmental authorities in accordance with those laws.

_Legal and Compliance_

We and our service providers may provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to another organization for the purposes of investigating a breach of an agreement or contravention of law or detecting, suppressing or preventing fraud, or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable Canadian, US or other law or legal process. Your personal information may also be disclosed where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims and to investigate or prevent actual or suspected loss or harm to persons or property.

_Sale of Business_

Personal information may be provided to third parties in connection with a merger or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of KEV Group or as part of a corporate reorganization or stock sale or other change in corporate control, including for the purpose of determining whether to proceed or continue with such transaction or business relationship. 

_**Safeguarding and Retention of Personal Information**_

We have implemented reasonable administrative, technical and physical measures in an effort to safeguard the personal information in our custody and control against theft, loss and unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure. We restrict access to your personal information on a need-to-know basis to employees and authorized service providers who require access to fulfill their job requirements.

We have personal information retention processes designed to retain personal information for no longer than necessary for the purposes stated above or to otherwise meet legal requirements.

_**Access to Personal Information**_

You may have the right to access, update and correct inaccuracies in your personal information in our custody and control, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. You may request access, updating and corrections of inaccuracies in other personal information we have in our custody or control by emailing or writing to us at the contact information set out below. We may request certain personal information for the purposes of verifying the identity of the individual seeking access to their personal information records.

_**Additional Information**_

_Third Party Websites_

The site may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us. We have no control over, do not review and are not responsible for the privacy policies of or content displayed on such other websites. When you click on such a link, you will leave our service and go to another site. During this process, another entity may collect personal information from you.

_Updates to the Privacy Policy_

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our privacy practices. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

_**Contact us**_

KEV Group welcomes your comments and questions regarding this Privacy Policy and the use of your personal information. If you have questions or concerns, please contact our Privacy Officer:

By email:  

By post:  
Privacy Officer  
KEV Group  
#200, 1167 Caledonia Road  
North York, ON M6A 2XI

\- or - 

Privacy Officer  
KEV Group  
990 Village Square, Suite G-800  
Tomball, TX, 77375
